[{"question": " oh, look at these! hey, ben. just do it. oh my god, oh, ok, was that too much pressure for him?", "answer": " you know, it's...something funny about sneakers. i'll be right back.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s2/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 1, "asentId": 2}, {"question": " i gotta get one, too.", "answer": " what are you guys doing?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s2/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 3, "asentId": 4}, {"question": " we're just hanging out by the spoons. ladle?", "answer": " look, would you guys grow up? that is the most natural beautiful thing in the world.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s2/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 5, "asentId": 6}, {"question": " yeah, we know, but there's a baby suckin' on it.", "answer": " this is my son having lunch, ok? it's gonna happen a lot, so you'd better get used to it. now if you have any problem with it, if you're uncomfortable, just ask questions. carol's fine with it, now come on.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s2/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 7, "asentId": 8}, {"question": " carol, carol? i was just wondering if joey could ask you a question about breast-feeding?", "answer": " sure.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s2/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 9, "asentId": 10}, {"question": " uh, does it hurt?", "answer": " it did at first, but not anymore.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s2/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 11, "asentId": 12}, {"question": " chandler?", "answer": " so, uh, how often can you do it?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s2/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 13, "asentId": 14}, {"question": " as much as he needs.", "answer": " ok, i got one, i got one. if he blows into one, does the other one get bigger? opening titles", "docId": "friendsCopy/s2/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 15, "asentId": 16}, {"question": " rachel, do you have any muffins left?", "answer": " yeah, i forget which ones.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s2/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 17, "asentId": 18}, {"question": " oh, you're busy, that's ok, i'll get it. anybody else want one? oh, you're losin' your apron here, let me get it. there you go.", "answer": " thank you. what a bitch.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s2/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 19, "asentId": 20}, {"question": " oh, listen you guys. i have this friend at bloomingdales who's quitting tomorrow and he wants to abuse his discount. so, anyone want to come with me and take advantage of it?", "answer": " i can't, i have to take my grandmother to the vet.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s2/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 21, "asentId": 22}, {"question": " ok, um, i'll go with you.", "answer": " great.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s2/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 23, "asentId": 24}, {"question": " hi, honey.", "answer": " hey, sweetums.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s2/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 25, "asentId": 26}, {"question": " hello to the rest.", "answer": " monica what're you doin'? you can't go shopping with her? what about rachel?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s2/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 27, "asentId": 28}, {"question": " it's gonna be a problem, isn't it?", "answer": " come on, you're going to bloomingdales with julie? that's like cheating on rachel in her house of worship.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s2/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 29, "asentId": 30}, {"question": " but i'm--", "answer": " monica, she will kill you. she will kill you like a dog in the street.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s2/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 31, "asentId": 32}, {"question": " so, uh, jules tells me you guys are going shopping tomorrow?", "answer": " yeah, uh, it's actually not that big a deal.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s2/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 33, "asentId": 34}, {"question": " it's a big deal to me. this is great, monica. i really appreciate this.", "answer": " you're welcome.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s2/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 35, "asentId": 36}, {"question": " woof, woof.", "answer": " bijan for men? hey annabelle.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s2/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 37, "asentId": 38}, {"question": " hey, joey. so did you hear about the new guy?", "answer": " who?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s2/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 39, "asentId": 40}, {"question": " nobody knows his name. me and the girls just call him the hombre man.", "answer": " what's he doin' in my section?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s2/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 41, "asentId": 42}, {"question": " i guess he doesn't know.", "answer": " well, he's gonna. i'll see you a little later, ok? hey, how ya doin'?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s2/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 43, "asentId": 44}, {"question": " mornin'.", "answer": " listen, i know you're new, but it's kinda understood that everything from young men's to the escalator is my territory.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s2/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 45, "asentId": 46}, {"question": " your territory, huh?", "answer": " yeah. bijan for men?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s2/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 47, "asentId": 48}, {"question": " no thanks.", "answer": " hombre?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s2/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 49, "asentId": 50}, {"question": " yeah. all right.", "answer": " you were saying?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s2/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 51, "asentId": 52}, {"question": " phoebe, listen. you were with me, and we were shopping all day.", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s2/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 53, "asentId": 54}, {"question": " we were shopping, and we had lunch.", "answer": " oh, all right. what did i have?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s2/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 55, "asentId": 56}, {"question": " you had a salad.", "answer": " oh, no wonder i don't feel full.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s2/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 57, "asentId": 58}, {"question": " hey, guys, what's up.", "answer": " i went shopping with monica all day, and i had a salad.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s2/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 59, "asentId": 60}, {"question": " good, pheebs. what'd you buy?", "answer": " um, we went shopping for um, for, fur.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s2/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 61, "asentId": 62}, {"question": " you went shopping for fur?", "answer": " yes, and then i realized i'm against that, and uh, so then we bought some, uh, boobs.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s2/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 63, "asentId": 64}, {"question": " you bought boobs?", "answer": " bras! we bought bras! we bought bras.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s2/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 65, "asentId": 66}, {"question": " bijan for men? hey, annabelle, uh, listen, i was wondering if maybe after work we could go maybe grab a cup of coffee.", "answer": " oh, actually i sorta have plans.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s2/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 67, "asentId": 68}, {"question": " ready, annabelle?", "answer": " you bet. maybe some other time?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s2/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 69, "asentId": 70}, {"question": " hey, it's not the first time i lost a girl to a cowboy spraying cologne. bijan for men?", "answer": " ok, and this is funny clown. funny clown is only for after his naps, not before his naps or he won't sleep.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s2/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 71, "asentId": 72}, {"question": " carol, we've been through this before, ok? we have a good time. we laugh, we play. it's like we're father and son.", "answer": " honey, relax. ross is great with him. don't look so surprised. i'm a lovely person.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s2/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 73, "asentId": 74}, {"question": " oh, this is so cute.", "answer": " oh, i got that for him.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s2/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 75, "asentId": 76}, {"question": " my mommies love me. that's clever.", "answer": " hello? oh, hi, ju-- hi, jew! uh huh? uh huh? ok. um, sure, that'd be great. see ya then. bye.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s2/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 77, "asentId": 78}, {"question": " did you just say hi, jew?", "answer": " yes. uh, yes, i did. that was my friend, eddie moskowitz. yeah, he likes it. reaffirms his faith.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s2/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 79, "asentId": 80}, {"question": " ben, dinner!", "answer": " thanks aunt pheebs. hey, you didn't microwave that, did you, because it's breast milk, and you're not supposed to do that.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s2/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 81, "asentId": 82}, {"question": " duh, i think i know how to heat breast milk. ok.", "answer": " what did you just do?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s2/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 83, "asentId": 84}, {"question": " i licked my arm, what?", "answer": " it's breast milk.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s2/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 85, "asentId": 86}, {"question": " so?", "answer": " phoebe, that is juice, squeezed from a person.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s2/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 87, "asentId": 88}, {"question": " what is the big deal?", "answer": " what did you just do?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s2/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 89, "asentId": 90}, {"question": " ok, would people stop drinking the breast milk?", "answer": " you won't even taste it?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s2/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 91, "asentId": 92}, {"question": " no!", "answer": " not even if you just pretend that it's milk?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s2/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 93, "asentId": 94}, {"question": " not even if carol's breast had a picture of a missing child on it.", "answer": " hey, where is everybody?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s2/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 95, "asentId": 96}, {"question": " they took ben to the park. where've you been?", "answer": " just out. had some lunch, just me, little quality time with me. thanks for your jacket.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s2/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 97, "asentId": 98}, {"question": " oh, no problem. you can borrow it, by the way. here are your keys, hon. mon, if uh you were at lunch alone, how come it cost you uh 53 dollars?", "answer": " you know what probably happened? someone musta stolen my credit card.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s2/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 99, "asentId": 100}, {"question": " and sorta just put the receipt back in your pocket", "answer": " that is an excellent excellent question. that is excellent.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s2/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 101, "asentId": 102}, {"question": " monica, what is with you? who'd you have lunch with?", "answer": " judy.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s2/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 103, "asentId": 104}, {"question": " who?", "answer": " julie.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s2/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 105, "asentId": 106}, {"question": " what?", "answer": " jody.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s2/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 107, "asentId": 108}, {"question": " you were with julie?", "answer": " look, when it started i was just trying to be nice to her because she was my brother's girlfriend. and then, one thing led to another and, before i knew it, we were...shopping.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s2/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 109, "asentId": 110}, {"question": " oh. oh my god.", "answer": " honey, wait. we only did it once. it didn't mean anything to me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s2/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 111, "asentId": 112}, {"question": " yeah, right.", "answer": " really, rachel, i was thinking of you the whole time. look, i'm sorry, all right. i never meant for you to find out.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s2/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 113, "asentId": 114}, {"question": " oh, please, you wanted to get caught.", "answer": " that is not true!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s2/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 115, "asentId": 116}, {"question": " oh, so you just sort of happened to leave it in here?", "answer": " did it ever occur to you that i might just be that stupid?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s2/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 117, "asentId": 118}, {"question": " ok, monica. i just have to know one thing. did you go with her to bloomingdales? oh! ok, ok, ok, i just really, uh, i just really need to not be with you right now.", "answer": " hi, who's this? hi, joanne. is rachel working? it's monica. yes, i know i did a horrible thing. joanna, it's not as simple as all that, ok? no, i don't care what steve thinks. hi, steve.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s2/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 119, "asentId": 120}, {"question": " how did we do?", "answer": " oh, i tasted ben's milk, and ross freaked out.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s2/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 121, "asentId": 122}, {"question": " i did not freak out.", "answer": " why'd you freak out?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s2/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 123, "asentId": 124}, {"question": " because it's breast milk. it's gross.", "answer": " my breast milk is gross?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s2/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 125, "asentId": 126}, {"question": " this should be fun.", "answer": " no, no, carol. there's nothing wrong with it. i just don't think breast milk is for adults.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s2/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 127, "asentId": 128}, {"question": " of course the packaging does appeal to grown-ups and kids alike.", "answer": " ross, you're being silly. i've tried it, it's no big deal. just taste it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s2/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 129, "asentId": 130}, {"question": " that would be no.", "answer": " come on. it doesn't taste bad.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s2/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 131, "asentId": 132}, {"question": " yeah, it's kinda sweet, sorta like, uh--", "answer": " cantaloupe juice.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s2/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 133, "asentId": 134}, {"question": " exactly.", "answer": " you've tasted it? you've tasted it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s2/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 135, "asentId": 136}, {"question": " uh huh.", "answer": " oh, you've tasted it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s2/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 137, "asentId": 138}, {"question": " you can keep saying it, but it won't stop being true.", "answer": " gimme the bottle. gimme the towel.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s2/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 139, "asentId": 140}, {"question": " howdy.", "answer": " gimme a box a juice. well, they switched me over to hombre.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s2/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 141, "asentId": 142}, {"question": " well, maybe it's because of the way you're dressed.", "answer": " or maybe it's because this guy's doing so good they wanna put more people on it. you should see this guy, chandler, he goes through two bottles a day.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s2/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 143, "asentId": 144}, {"question": " what do you care? you're an actor. this is your day job. this isn't supposed to mean anything to you.", "answer": " i know, but, i was the best, you know? i liked being the best. i don't know. maybe i should just get outta the game. they need guys up in housewares to serve cheese.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s2/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 145, "asentId": 146}, {"question": " all right, say you do that. you know sooner or later somebody's gonna come along that slices a better cheddar. and then where're you gonna run?", "answer": " yeah i guess you're right.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s2/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 147, "asentId": 148}, {"question": " you're damn right i'm right. i say you show this guy what you're made of. i say you stand your ground. i say you show him that you are the baddest hombre west of the lingerie.", "answer": " i'm gonna do it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s2/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 149, "asentId": 150}, {"question": " all right. now go see miss kitty and she'll fix you up with a nice hooker.", "answer": " i don't know what else to say.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s2/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 151, "asentId": 152}, {"question": " well that works out good, because i'm not listening.", "answer": " i feel terrible, i really do.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s2/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 153, "asentId": 154}, {"question": " oh, i'm sorry, did my back hurt your knife?", "answer": " rachel, say that i'm friends with her, we spend some time together. is that so terrible?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s2/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 155, "asentId": 156}, {"question": " yes.", "answer": " it's that terrible?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s2/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 157, "asentId": 158}, {"question": " yes. monica, you don't get it. it's bad enough that she's stolen the guy who might actually be the person that i am supposed to be with, but now, she's actually, but now she's actually stealing you.", "answer": " me? what are you talking about? nobody could steal me from you. i mean, just because i'm friends with her doesn't make me any less friends with you. i mean, you're my...we're, we're...oh, i love you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s2/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 159, "asentId": 160}, {"question": " i love you too.", "answer": " you guys, um i know that this really doesn't have anything to do with me, but um i love you guys too. oh, i really needed that.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s2/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 161, "asentId": 162}, {"question": " look, i know that you're in a place right now where you really need to hate julie's guts, but she didn't do anything wrong. i mean, she was just a girl who met a guy, and now they go out. i really think that if you gave her a chance, you'd like her. would you just give that a chance, for me?", "answer": " i'd do anything for you, you know that.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s2/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 163, "asentId": 164}, {"question": " i'd do anything for you.", "answer": " wait, wait, wait, wait!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s2/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 165, "asentId": 166}, {"question": " mornin'. i said, mornin'.", "answer": " i heard ya.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s2/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 167, "asentId": 168}, {"question": " all right, everybody, i'm openin' the doors. you boys ready?", "answer": " ready.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s2/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 169, "asentId": 170}, {"question": " yeah, i'm ready.", "answer": " you idiot, you stupid cowboy, you blinded me, i'm suing!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s2/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 171, "asentId": 172}, {"question": " oh my god, todd! what the hell did you do?", "answer": " i'm sorry. i am such a doofus. i'm so sorry, i'm so sorry.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s2/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 173, "asentId": 174}, {"question": " my god, what happened?", "answer": " these new kids, they never last. sooner or later, they all...stop lastin'. listen, uh, what do you say i buy you that cup of coffee now?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s2/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 175, "asentId": 176}, {"question": " sure.", "answer": " so.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s2/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 177, "asentId": 178}, {"question": " so. i just thought the two of us should hang out for a bit. i mean, you know, we've never really talked. i guess you'd know that, being one of the two of us, though, right?", "answer": " i know, i probably shouldn't even tell you this, but i'm pretty much totally intimidated by you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s2/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 179, "asentId": 180}, {"question": " really? me?", "answer": " yes. oh my god, are you kidding? ross is so crazy about you, and i really wanted you to like me, and, it's probably me being totally paranoid, but i kinda got the feeling that maybe you don't.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s2/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 181, "asentId": 182}, {"question": " well, you're not totally paranoid.", "answer": " oy.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s2/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 183, "asentId": 184}, {"question": " um, ok, uh, oh god, um, when you and uh ross first started going out, it was really hard for me, um, for many reasons, which i'm not gonna bore you with now, but um, i just, i see how happy he is, you know, and how good you guys are together, and um, monica's always saying how nice you are, and god i hate it when she's right.", "answer": " thanks. hey, listen, would you like to go to a movie sometime or something?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s2/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 185, "asentId": 186}, {"question": " yeah, that'd be great. i'd love it.", "answer": " i'd love it too. shoot, i gotta go. so, i'll talk to you later.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s2/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 187, "asentId": 188}]